I'm hoping and remember what they say in
in business school hope is not a
strategy but I'm hoping that Donald
Trump is sincere about ending the war in
Ukraine about staying out of other
Count's
business about leaving Syria to its own
devices and about
some sort of an agreement eventually
somehow with the government of Iran
otherwise I don't think we're going to
get it from some of these other players
I also wanted to talk for a minute or
two about Senator Marco
Rubio I'm as mystified as anybody as to
why in the world Donald Trump chose
Marco Rubio to be Secretary of State
Marco Rubio is is a republican in the
mold of George W bush and any every
other neoconservative that came before
him he's known for his
especially um hardcore stances against
Cuba and against
Venezuela I was very fortunate a year
ago to go to Cuba and uh and to see it
for myself and to meet with average
Cubans on the street and and official
Cubans up to uh one of the vice
presidents of the country uh with whom a
group of us uh Americans had dinner and
talked about Rel ations between our two
countries I'm not at all sanguin that
Donald Trump or Marco Rubio on behalf of
Donald Trump is going to do anything at
all to improve us relations with Cuba I
think the situation with Ben as whale is
worse I think that that what we're going
to see under Donald Trump is a
continuation of the Joe Biden policy on
Venezuela which in turn was a
continuation of the first Donald Trump
policy toward Venezuela I think we're
going to remain in a virtual state of
war with that country and nothing good
is going to come of it